<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="language">Language</string>
    <string name="shared_preferences">sharedpreferences</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_language">language</string>
    <string name="app_name">PMDM Task 2</string>
    <string name="name_mario">Mario</string>
    <string name="desc_mario">The main hero of the Mushroom Kingdom. Mario is very positive and always.
        He is happy. You can recognize him by his blue overalls, his red cap and his
        characteristic mustache. Princess Peach considers him her trusted friend, and everyone does.
        She knows him and his brother Luigi for their acts of bravery. Mario excels in sports
        such as tennis, golf, baseball, soccer and even kart racing. It is good in all
        sports! He is a plumber by profession, but the truth is that he is a jack of all trades.</string>
    <string name="skill_mario">Mario uses his powerful jumping ability and a large amount
            of upgrades to face his archenemy, Bowser.
    </string>


    <string name="name_luigi">Luigi</string>
    <string name="desc_luigi">Mario\'s brother and hero of the Mushroom Kingdom. Luigi is
        recognized instantly by his green cap and shirt. Luigi is friendly, but a little nervous,
        especially if there are ghosts around. However, their abilities match Mario\'s abilities,
        so when these brothers come together, there is nothing they cannot achieve.</string>
    <string name="skill_luigi"> Luigi is taller and can jump higher than Mario. If you pay attention,
        You may also notice that the shape of his mustache is a little different as well.
    </string>


    <string name="name_peach">Princess Peach</string>
    <string name="desc_peach">The beloved princess of the Mushroom Kingdom. He is extremely kind and
        is always working to create a world in which everyone can live together happily.
        Her famous pink dress is charming.
        Princess Peach is always ready to participate in a wide variety of sports, and
        She also loves to bake and cook.
    </string>
    <string name="skill_peach">She and Mario are very good friends and are always willing to
        Help each other when you can.
    </string>

    <string name="name_toad">Toad</string>
    <string name="desc_toad">Resident of the Mushroom Kingdom, he works in the service of Princess Peach.
        Toad has red spots on his head, although others of his species come in a variety of
        colors.
    </string>
    <string name="skill_toad">Toad is very happy and loyal. He does everything he can to help Mario and Luigi in their endeavors.
        to protect the Mushroom Kingdom from Bowser, even if it means facing danger
        during the process.

    </string>
    <string name="name_bowser">Bowser</string>
    <string name="desc_bowser">The king of the Koopas. Bowser is Mario\'s archenemy and always
        is wreaking havoc on the Mushroom Kingdom. Bowser has many henchmen who
        They include the Koopas, Goombas, Bill Bala and Shy Guys. Every time you look at the
        Mushroom Kingdom\'s plans are thwarted by Mario and his friends.
    </string>
    <string
        name="skill_bowser"> Este poderoso enemigo posee una gran fuerza y hasta puede escupir fuego.
    </string>



    <string name="name_yoshi">Yoshi</string>
    <string name="desc_yoshi">Mario\'s trusty companion from Yoshi\'s Island. It is green, but others of its species come in other colors, such as red, blue, pink and yellow.</string>
    <string name="skill_yoshi">Yoshi is friendly and calm. It uses its long tongue to eat fruits and enemies, which it can turn into eggs that it can throw.</string>

    <string name="name_donkey_kong">Donkey Kong</string>
    <string name="desc_donkey_kong">The king of the jungle is distinguished by a red tie with his initials.</string>
    <string name="skill_donkey_kong">Donkey Kong can throw gigantic barrels with the greatest of ease, and his strength is so great that the ground shakes every time he hits it.</string>

    <string name="name_wario">Wario</string>
    <string name="desc_wario">Mario\'s self-proclaimed archenemy. Wario wears purple overalls, a yellow cap, and has a zigzag mustache that you\'ll instantly recognize.
    </string>
    <string name="skill_wario">He has a loud personality and doesn\'t worry about the little things. He loves garlic and money.</string>
    <string name="aplicacion_desarrollada_por">Application developed by Javier, version 1.0</string>
    <string name="acerca_de">About:</string>
    <string name="marioapp">MarioApp</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the Mario\'s world</string>
    <string name="select_pj">Character has been selected</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open menú: </string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close menú: </string>
    <string name="drawer_header_title">Drawer tittle: </string>
    <string name="drawer_header_text">Drawer text: </string>
    <string name="radiobutton_text_spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="radiobutton_text_english">English\n</string>
    <string name="preferences_app">App preferences</string>
    <string name="language_selected_spanish">Spanish</string>
    <string name="language_selected_english">English</string>



</resources>

